=Let's Go Fighting= =Episode 8=
= لنبدأ القتال = = الحلقة 8 =
Mu Liu,
مو ليو ،
you can't get away from me.
لا يمكنك الابتعاد عني.
Who?
من؟
(Hello, your takeout.)
(مرحبًا ، تناول الطعام بالخارج.)
Wrong place.
مكان خاطئ.
(No, it's Room 5188.)
(لا ، إنها غرفة 5188.)
Who?
من؟
You pervert!
أنت المنحرف!
What?
ماذا؟
Just after being drunk and acting crazy,
فقط بعد أن كنت ثملاً وتصرفت بجنون ،
you were trying to kill me?
كنت تحاول قتلي؟
Look,
نظرة،
that's what you did.
هذا ما فعلته.
What?
ماذا؟
No.
رقم.
So my clothes were...
لذلك كانت ملابسي ...
Stop.
قف.
A waitress did it.
نادلة فعلت ذلك.
New clothes are coming.
ملابس جديدة قادمة.
Oh.
أوه.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Next time,
المرة التالية،
don't flaunt your superiority.
لا تتباهى بتفوقك.
OK.
نعم.
Got it.
فهمتك.
Now you believe me?
الآن أنت تصدقني؟
Yes.
نعم.
Then can you
ثم يمكنك
accompany me back to the birthday party?
رافقني مرة أخرى إلى حفلة عيد الميلاد؟
(Flora Island) (I put a recorder pen in my bag.)
(فلورا آيلاند) (وضعت قلم تسجيل في حقيبتي).
(Now we need to get this pen back quickly.)
(نحتاج الآن إلى استعادة هذا القلم بسرعة.)
Then how can you get it back?
ثم كيف يمكنك استعادتها؟
What are you trying to do?
ماذا تحاول أن تفعل؟
Aunt.
عمة.
Liu,
ليو ،
weren't you with Song Yuan?
ألم تكن مع سونغ يوان؟
I asked him to prepare the agreement documents.
طلبت منه إعداد وثائق الاتفاقية.
Well then,
حسنا اذن،
let's celebrate in advance.
دعونا نحتفل مقدما.
Hello, Ms. Mu.
مرحبا سيدة مو.
I've been looking for you.
لقد كنت ابحث عنك.
You came just in time.
لقد أتيت في الوقت المناسب.
Have a drink with Ms. Mu
تناول مشروبًا مع السيدة مو
for me, OK?
بالنسبة لي طيب؟
Ms. Mu,
السّيدة.  في،
happy birthday.
عيد مولد سعيد.
Oh,
أوه،
it's a great honor.
إنه لشرف عظيم.
You're really the star here, Ms. Mu.
أنت حقا النجمة هنا ، السيدة مو.
You are the most gorgeous tonight.
أنت أجمل هذه الليلة.
With you here, Mr. Mo,
معك هنا ، سيد مو ،
I'm totally overshadowed.
أنا طغت تماما.
Ms. Mu,
السّيدة.  في،
excuse me,
عفوا،
I need to go to the restroom.
أحتاج للذهاب إلى غرفة الاستراحة.
Well,
نحن سوف،
let me take you there.
دعني آخذك إلى هناك.
I was surprised,
كنت متفاجئا،
Mr. Mo.
السيد.  مو.
What a nice trick with your beauty.
يا لها من خدعة جميلة بجمالك.
Never again.
لن يحدث مطلقا مرة اخري.
You are mean!
انت منحط!
Come on.
هيا.
Yuan,
يوان،
I find that Mu Liu
أجد أن مو ليو
(is like a different person now.)
(مثل شخص مختلف الآن.)
(What did she say about the shares?)
(ماذا قالت عن الأسهم؟)
(Forget it.)
(انسى ذلك.)
She just gave me a bag.
لقد أعطتني حقيبة للتو.
No matter how she changes,
مهما تغيرت ،
she can't get away from me.
لا يمكنها الابتعاد عني.
(Do whatever it takes)
(قم بكل ما يلزم)
(to get the shares.)
(للحصول على الأسهم).
(Don't worry, baby.)
(لا تقلق يا حبيبي.)
Just wait and see how I get her tonight.
فقط انتظر وانظر كيف سأحصل عليها الليلة.
I'll kick her out of the way
سوف أطردها من الطريق
(when she gives all her shares to us.)
(عندما تعطينا كل حصصها).
What a terrible couple!
يا له من زوجين رهيبين!
Wait!
انتظر!
Don't be impulsive!
لا تكن مندفعًا!
Let's go back and discuss it.
دعنا نعود ونناقشها.
(Flora Island)
(جزيرة فلورا)
Mu Liu.
مو ليو.
Look at what you've done.
انظر إلى ما قمت به.
=Let's Go Fighting=
= لنبدأ القتال =
♪The soul falls to the bottom of the lake♪
الروح تسقط في قاع البحيرة
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪ النجوم المكسورة تخترق السماء ♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪